A Guide to the Memorabilia FA437
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1
  - paperweight, 180th anniversary, Veterans Corps of Artillery, 1970; see #690 (Object 612, Box 23)
  - paperweight, inscription from R.J.R w/ Roosevelt quote, 1970; see #65 (Object 613, Box 23)
  - paperweight, memento of trip to Israel, from Ken Richard, 1972 August (Object 614, Box 37)
  - paperweight, NY Committee to Re-elect the President, 1972 (Object 615, Box 23)
  - paperweight, Ticonderoga Mill International Paper Company, 1972 October 21 (Object 616, Box 23)
  - marble book ends, Community Mayors of NYS; matches #516, see #408, 516, 712 (Object 617, Box 17)
  - 2 metal bookends from Godkin Lecture at Harvard, Mayor Crane, 1962 February (Object 618, Box 20)
  - gavel, N. Tarrytown Convention Committee, w/ medal, 1962 June 22; see #764 (Object 619, Box 23)
  - gavel, Ernest Sonderegger from Homestead National Monument, NE (Object 620, Box 23)
  - inscribed plaque from Green Bay Packers, 1975 (Object 621, Box 19)
  - plaque, groundbreaking at NYCMCC, 1970 October 18 (Object 622, Box 19)
  - plaque from Town Hall of California (Object 623, Box 19)
  - paperweight, President of Brand Cold Mining Co., 1956 July 19 (Object 624, Box 19)
  - paperweight, from Town of Hamburg, Erie County Fair, 1962 (Object 625, Box 19)
  - 2 paperweights, New York State Day, NY World's Fair, 1964 April 23; see #638 (Object 626, Box 19)
  - 2 paperweights, Peppy Partners 4H Club, Cayuga County, see #519, 862 (Object 627, Box 19)
  - paperweight, from Teddy Kollek, Mayor of Jerusalem (Object 628, Box 19)
  - plaque, Regional Plan Association 40th Anniversary, 1969 November 18; 11 x 7 x 4 (Object 629, Box 19)
  - Boypower-Manpower Award, Boy Scouts of America Boy Scout Week, 1969; 4 x 4 x 4; see #122 (Object 630, Box 19)
  - salute to First Lady of NYS, Federation of Jewish Women's Orgs., 1967 March 29; 3.5 x 5.5 x 7.5 (Object 631, Box 19)
  - dedication of Verrazano-Narrows Bridge, Bridge & Tunnel Authority, 1964 November 21; 3.25 x 4.25 x 4.5 (Object 632, Box 19)
  - model of Italia Terraco Restaurant, 2.75 x 2.75 x 5.25 (Object 633, Box 19)
  - paperweight, Board of Trustees of Ramon Magsaysay Award, 1958 August 31; 2 x 4 x 4.5 (Object 634, Box 19)
  - paperweight "Strengthen America Your Decision Can Make the Difference", Boy Scouts of America, 2.5 x 2.75; see #122 (Object 635, Box 19)
  - 2 Nixon medals & commemorative paperweight, 1968; see #675 for identical medals (Object 636, Box 19)
  - Speaker's Award, Sales Executives Club of New York, w/ note, 1970 October 16; 3 x 3 x 3.25 (Object 637, Box 19)
  - paperweight, opening day of NY World's Fair, 1965; 1.5 x 1.25 x 4.75 (Object 638, Box 19)
  - gavel w/plaque, Republican's Conference in Williamsburg VA, 1971 April; 8.25 x 3.5; see #268 for list of related (Object 639, Box 16)
  - large wooden Key to Hawaii, Chairman Kimura, w/ engraved plate, 1967 July 6; 15 x 4.5; damaged. (Object 640, Box 17)
  - key to Long Beach, CA, from Mayor Edwin W. Wade, w/ card, 1960 September 16; 6 x 2 (Object 641, Box 19)
  - key to Columbia, SC, from Mayor Lester Bates, w/card, 6 x 2.5 (Object 642, Box 19)
  - symbolic key, Adjutants General Association NYC, w/engraved plate, 1962 May 2; 9.75 x 4 x 0.5 (Object 643, Box 19)
  - key to Auburn NY, 6.25 x 2 (Object 644, Box 19)
  - key to Ocean City MD, Mayor Harry Kelley, 8 x 2.5 (Object 645, Box 19)
  - key to Dallas TX, Mayor Wes Wise, w/ note, 5 x 1.75 (Object 646, Box 17)
  - unidentified heart-shaped padlock w/ key, 1967; 3 x 2.5 (Object 647, Box 19)
  - medal, Commander and Officers Khyber Rifles, Pakistan, 7 x 0.75 (Object 648, Box 23)
  - Man of the Year Award, Mid City Republican Club, 1970; 7" diameter (Object 649, Box 22)
  - Republic of the Phillipines Proof Set, Central Bank, 1976 (Object 650, Box 23)
  - Franklin Award for Distinguished Service, Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York, 1970; 2.5" diameter; see # 159, 222 (Object 651, Box 23)
  - bronze medal from Stanley Woodward on behalf of President of Chile, 1950 April 16; 3" diameter (Object 652, Box 23)
  - bronze medal from visit of President of Brazil, dinner at Pocantico, 1949 May; 3" diameter (Object 653, Box 23)
  - medal, Foundation for Research of the NY Academy of Osteopathy, 1965 January 23; 3" diameter; see #295 (Object 654, Box 23)
  - Missouri Sesquicentennial coin, 1970; 1.5" diameter (Object 655, Box 23)
  - medal in display from Iowa Governor Robert D. Ray, 3" diameter (Object 656, Box 23)
  - 25 year commemorative coin, Kenneth H. Ripen Company Inc w/note, 1955; 3.5 x 3.75 (Object 657, Box 23)
  - 50 year commemorative coin, New York Hotel & Motel Association, 1965; 3" diameter; see #205 (Object 658, Box 23)
  - bronze coin from Mayor Kaoruchuma of Osaka, 2.75" diameter (Object 659, Box 23)
  - inscribed coin from French Senate, 1969; 1.5" diameter; see #557, 691 (Object 660, Box 23)
  - coin from 75th anniversary, Zionist Org. of America Convention, 1972 July; 2.25 diameter (Object 661, Box 23)
  - heart-shaped medal in appreciation, The Seraphics, 2 x 2.5 x 0.5 (Object 662, Box 23)
  - 2 Inscribed medals, Presidential Mission to Latin America, 1969 Summer; 2.5" diameter; see #773, 830 (Object 663, Box 20)
  - anniversary. medal, from NY Public Library, Astor, Lenox & Tilden Foundations, 1961 May 23; 3.25" diameter; see #541 (Object 664, Box 23)
  - Cultural Center of Philippines medal, from First Lady Marcos, 3" diameter (Object 665, Box 23)
  - medal, National Conference of Christians and Jews, Brotherhood Week, 1949; 2" diameter (Object 667, Box 23)
  - medal, village of Dobbs Ferry, NY Centennial Celebration, 1973; 1.5" diameter (Object 668, Box 23)
  - Republican Centennial Commemorative medal, w/ note, 1954; 2.5" diameter (Object 669, Box 23)
  - medal, National Museum of Racing & Hall of Fame, Saratoga Springs NY, 1955 (?); 3" diameter (Object 670, Box 22)
  - medal, Governor G. Mennen Williams of Michigan, 1949-1960; 1.5" diameter (Object 671, Box 22)
  - 3 medals, Yisrael Yeshayahu, Speaker of the Knesset, Jerusalem, 1975 November; 3 x 7 olive wood box (Object 672, Box 22)
  - 4 medallions from United Jewish Appeal of Greater New York, 1972 July; in olive wood box; see #251,563,583,817,891 (Object 673, Box 22)
  - 2 medallions, President Zalman Shazar of Israel, in olive wood box (Object 674, Box 22)
  - 2 bronze medals in case "With deep appreciation-Richard Nixon", 1968; see #636 for identical (Object 676, Box 22)
  - bronze medal, Salvation Army Centennial, 1965; see #597 (Object 676, Box 22)
  - Emory Bucknell Medal, Federal Bar Council (14k gold), 1969; 1.5" diameter; see #701 (Object 677, Box 22)
  - coin from Expo '74 World's Fair Spokane WA, 1974; 1.5" diameter (Object 678, Box 22)
  - Gdansk, Poland Centennial coin in leather case, 1962; 2.25" diameter (Object 679, Box 22)
  - papal medallion from St. Peter's Basilica, 2.25" diameter (Object 680, Box 22)
  - Terence Cardinal Cooke D.D. medal, 1969; 2.5" diameter (Object 681, Box 37)
  - Official National Independence Day Weekend coin, 1976 July 4; 2.5" diameter (Object 682, Box 37)
  - Niagara County Community College SUNY coin, 1962; 3.5" diameter (Object 683, Box 37)
  - Great Seal of the State of Arizona coin w/ AZ flag pin, 3.25" diameter (Object 684, Box 37)
  - bronze Commercial Bank of Italy coin, w/ note, 1969 December 1; 2.75" diameter (Object 685, Box 22)
  - Tor Janer commemorative medal, Brazil, 1951; 2" diameter (Object 686, Box 22)
  - 2 gold medals on ribbons, Pan American Society, 1944 May 17; 4 x 6 box (Object 687, Box 22)
  - Order of Merit, Chile: 2 medals with ribbons, note, 1945 September; see #573 (Object 688, Box 22)
  - 10k gold medal, International Supreme Council, Order of DeMolay, 8 x 7 (Object 689, Box 22)
  - medal w/ duplicate, Veterans Corps of Artillery, NY 1790, see #612 (Object 690, Box 22)
  - Order of Arts and Humanities, Republic of France, see #557, 660 (Object 691, Box 22)
  - 14k leadership medal, Benjamin Franklin Society, box 20 (Object 692, Box 22)
  - honorary member, Future Farmers of America-2 medals, 1975; MEDALS MISSING FROM CASE; see #124,431 (Object 693, Box 22)
  - medal, Bar Association of Nassau County NY, 1974 May 23; box 20 (Object 694, Box 22)
  - medal, United States Information Agency, 1957; box 20 (Object 695, Box 22)
  - medal, State Special Olympics/Kennedy Foundation, see #739; box 20 (Object 696, Box 22)
  - Royal Order of the Cardinal medal (Object 697, Box 22)
  - Friend of the City medal, Sao Paulo, Brazil: 2 badges w/card, see #98,572,700; box 20 (Object 698, Box 22)
  - Monroe County Medallion, Monroe County Legislature, w/ flag pin, 1970 April 7; in a wooden box with glass display (Object 699, Box 22)
  - Benemerentium Praemium, Brazil: 2 medals on ribbons, see #98,572,698 (Object 700, Box 24)
  - Emory Buckner Medal, Federal Bar Council (10k gold), see #677 (Object 701, Box 24)
  - Commander, Order of Dannebrog 1st Class, Royal Danish Consulate, 2 crosses w/ card (Object 702, Box 24)
  - medal and flag pin, American Women's Union, Caracas Venezuela, 1944 (Object 703, Box 37)
  - medal, 55th Annual NYS United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Convention, Niagara Falls NY, 1961 September (Object 704, Box 37)
  - 52nd Building & Construction Trades Dept AFL-CIO Convention, 1963 November (Object 705, Box 37)
  - 2 unidentified medals, a star-shaped and a cross-shaped (Object 706, Box 24)
  - 2 unidentified medals w/ eagle emblem (Object 707, Box 24)
  - unidentified medal w/ eagle emblem in matching case, possibly related to #580 (Object 708, Box 24)
  - 2 copies of book of photos & quotes from Wallace K. Harrison, from dinner from American Association for the UN, 1952 October 23; 14.75 x 11 (Object 709, Box 57)
  - portfolio of pamphlets etc, Arsham Foundation, Kerman, Iran, 10.25 x 14.5; documents stored separately (Object 710, Box 57)
  - portfolio of pamphlets etc, Arsham Foundation, Kerman, Iran, documents. (Object 710, Box 91)
  - small weaving "Rose Tapestry" by Eia Lampe, FIT, 1965; 10.5 x 14; in black slipcase (Object 711, Box 57)
  - Man of the Year album (no photos), Community Mayors of NYS, 1970; 11 x 13; see #408,516,617 (Object 713, Box 37)
  - empty address book embossed w/date & seal of NY state, 1972 December; 6.5 x 6.25 (Object 713, Box 37)
  - "Peace is America's Goal" license plate, 6 x 12 (Object 715, Box 24)
  - pen used by LBJ to sign HR 2580 amendment to Immigration Act w/ note, 1965 October 18 (Object 715, Box 24)
    given by Jack Valenti
  - copy of letter from NAR to Joseph Ryback about posters, 1968 September 12; 8.5 x 11 (Object 716, Box 91)
  - "Gov. Wrights' Grand March", musical score by Oliver J. Shaw, sent from NYS Historical Society to Mrs. Arnold Miles, Washington D.C., 1956 November 10 (Object 718, Box 46)
  - Improving Songs for Anxious Children by John & Rue Carpenter, w/ card, 1962 November 22; 10.75 x 14.75 (Object 719, Box 46)
  - "21" red and white scarf from Jack & Charlie (Object 720, Box 46)
  - Inaugural Ball commemorative scarf, #34 of 100 made, w/ pamphlet, 1969 January 20 (Object 721, Box 24)
  - Bicentennial Pin in case, 1976 (Object 721, Box 24)
  - 2 Kentucky Derby pins, each in own case, 1969; see #878 (Object 722, Box 24)
  - 2 gold cuff links w/ 2 tie pins, Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1971; see #395 (Object 723, Box 24)
  - set of cuff links w/ seal of Idaho and NY, broken (Object 724, Box 24)
  - money clip w/ seal of NY (Object 725, Box 24)
  - tie clasp, RNC President's Club (Object 726, Box 24)
  - 14k gold charm, National Governor's Conference, 1970; see # 268 for list of related (Object 727, Box 24)
  - charm w/ seal of W. VA, inscribed "Margaretta", Gov's Conference, 1966; see # 520, 268 (Object 728, Box 24)
  - charm, 450th Anniversary of Puerto Rico, 63rd Gov's Conference, 1971; see #555, 268 (Object 729, Box 24)
  - 2 inscribed charms, 1970 November 3 (Object 730, Box 24)
  - medal "With Thanks", 1970 November 3; accompanies #730 (Object 731, Box 24)
  - 5 gold pins "Rocky" with elephant (Object 732, Box 24)
  - pin from Yankees 32nd World Series, 1978 (Object 733, Box 24)
  - 10k gold Alpha Zeta pin, from Cornell, 1962 April 14; see #165, 810 (Object 734, Box 24)
  - 6 honorary membership cards: Syracuse University Alumni; Bricklayers, Masons, Plasterers International Union; Uniformed Fire Officers Association; Philadelphia Museum of Art; Police Conference of NY; American Football League (Official League Pass), 1965; all stored together in yellow envelope; see #241 (Object 735, Box 24)
  - campaign sticker, 4 pins and ribbon from Dartmouth, w/ pamphlet, 1963; see #86, 334 (Object 736, Box 91)
  - Cornell University Council manual, 1961-1962 (Object 737, Box 91)
  - speech for recording on behalf of Red Cross, 1960 February 16; 8 typed pages (Object 738, Box 91)
  - NYS Special Olympics Band Album-9 unopened copies of LP, 1972 August; see #696; REMOVED TO A/V COLLECTION. (Object 740)
  - "Love Cry of the Soul" album, Rev. Idele Cordett- 3 records, 1963-1965 (Object 741)
  - album by Corina Parral de Velasco Ibarra, inscribed to Mrs. NAR (Object 742)
  - 2 records from 176th Anniversary. of Society of Friendly Sons of St. Patrick, 1960 March 17 (Object 743)
  - sound filmstrips & 2 laps, "State Government in Action: Portrait of Governor NAR" w/ pamphlet, 1969 (Object 744, Box 61)
  - negatives of CIAA charts from NAR Washington files, 1951 November; slides are 5.5 x 4.5 (Object 744, Box 61)
  - plaque, Brockway Motor Trucks Cortlandt NY, 1962; 4 x 7 x 11 (Object 745, Box 37)
  - quill used to dedicate Old Supreme Court Chamber at U.S. Capitol, 1975 May 22; 6.25 x 16.75 x 6.25 (Object 746)
  - rock from the Great Wall, Peking, from Dr. Kenneth Riland D.O., 1972 February; in 5 x 5 x 5 plastic box (Object 747, Box 17)
  - Humanitarian Award, United Cerebral Palsy, 1963 January 11; 6.75 x 9 x 5.25; see #370, 426 (Object 748, Box 58)
  - Humanitarian Award, Hofstra University, 1976 October 27; 5.5 x 5.5 x 4; see #421 (Object 749, Box 24)
  - gold engraved bell, New York Women's Council, 1962 April 10; 10 x 5.75 diameter (Object 750, Box 16)
  - silver menorah, Anti-Defamation League of B'Nai B'rith, 3.5 x 5 x 7.5; see #358 (Object 752, Box 25)
  - hard hat, Elia Niagara Falls New York "NAR JR" (Object 752, Box 25)
  - hard hat, Urban Development Corporation in Newburgh (Object 753, Box 25)
  - hard hat "Rocky", "Labor likes Rocky" (Object 754, Box 25)
  - hard hat, Elia Niagara Falls New York "Mark Rockefeller" (Object 755, Box 25)
  - hard hat, Groveton Papers Co, NH "Vote NAR March 10" (Object 756, Box 26)
  - hard hat "Gov Rockefeller" (Object 757, Box 26)
  - hard hat, town of Islip, Long Island NY "Gov Rockefeller" (Object 758, Box 26)
  - hard hat, "Chief" (Object 759, Box 26)
  - hard hat, "SUNY Construction Fund" (Object 760, Box 27)
  - hard hat, International Union of Operating Engineers, Local #138, Hempstead (Object 761, Box 27)
  - safari hat, Mesabi Range, Hibbing "Rocky" (Object 762, Box 27)
  - firefighter's hat, West Carthage F.D. Chief (Object 763, Box 28)
  - firefighter's hat, Nyack NY (Object 765, Box 28)
  - old fashioned policeman's hat, gray wool, with number 7 on front (Object 768, Box 29)
  - business cards, Executive Chamber, Albany NY (Object 769, Box 37)
  - "Happy Birthday Ike" poster, 22 x 17 (Object 772, Box 20)
  - gold key chain w/ elephant (Object 772, Box 20)
  - NYS desk set: silver cup and keychain, 1964 (Object 774, Box 52)
  - 6 maps of craft union jurisdictions, Building Industry Employers NYS, 20 x 30; see #179 (Object 775, Box 52)
  - wooden hands sculpture, Sales Executives Club of New York, 1965 September 28; 6 x 2.75 x 5 (Object 776, Box 20)
  - animal carving by A. Mwariko, Kiluahanyaro, Tanzia, sent via Roland Elliot, 10 x 6 (Object 777, Box 20)
  - wooden desk piece "Gov NAR", 6 x 3 x 5 (Object 778, Box 20)
  - paperweight from W.H. St. Thomas w/ NYS building inside dome, 1964-1965; 4 x 4.5 diameter, missing weight (Object 779, Box 20)
  - small silver trowel, Mary Manning Walsh Nursing Home, 1967 September 18; 15.5 x 5; see #70 (Object 780, Box 20)
  - small clay elephant, from Clover, Nassau NY, 7 x 5 (Object 781, Box 20)
  - sterling silver pencil cup, from Louisville, France, 3 x 3.75 (Object 782, Box 20)
  - metal fan-shaped letter holder decorated with zodiac mosaic, 4 x 2.5 (Object 783, Box 20)
  - clock, President Lemus of El Salvador, 1969; 2.5 x 5 x 6.25 (Object 784, Box 85)
  - barometer/thermometer, Hornell Consolidated School District, 1966; 4.5 x 10 (Object 785, Box 36)
  - carved gourd, Francisco Veray Aragon, Coronel from Paraguay, 7.5 x 5.25 (Object 786, Box 36)
  - cigarette lighter in the shape of Seattle Space Needle, 10.25 high (Object 788, Box 16)
  - cigarette lighter in shape of fire hat, Uniformed Firemen's Assoc., 1968 April 1; 5.25 x 4.5 x 2.75 (Object 789, Box 36)
  - artillery shell from salute at Inauguration, NYARNG Kingston NY, 1971 January 1; 5.5 x 5.5 x 6; see #836, 908 (Object 790, Box 16)
  - artillery shell from salute at Inauguration, NYARNG Kingston NY, 1963 January 1; 5.5 x 5.5 x 6; see #836, 908 (Object 791, Box 16)
  - bust of Winston Churchill, 6 x 6 x 18.5 (Object 792)
  - plaster bust of NAR, 6.5 x 11.5 x 16.5 (Object 793)
  - wood bust of Nigerian woman, from opening of Oswego Port, Nigeria, 5.25 x 7 x 13.5; in Norine's office (Object 794, Box 39)
  - Humanitarian Award, Assoc. for the Help of Retarded Children, 1966 June 18; 10 x 14 x 3 (Object 795, Box 39)
  - Bicentennial gift, Trustees of the Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1976 June 10; 12 x 17 x 4; see #32 (Object 796, Box 42)
  - model of log cabin, 8.5 x 16 x 8 (Object 797, Box 42)
  - wooden suitcase, 20 x 26 x 7.5 (Object 798)
  - carved box from Indian ambassador, locked w/out key with 4 empty canisters inside, sent by T.N. Kaul, Indian ambassador, 1974 December; 18 x 18 x 8.5 (Object 799)
  - miniature Japanese Samurai helmet in wooden display box, 1959 September 25; 11 x 11 x 13 (Object 801, Box 34)
  - Meritorious Service Award, NYS Assoc. of Junior Colleges, 14.5 diameter (Object 802, Box 34)
  - decorative chess set of nuts and bolts, 12.5 x 12.5 x 2 (Object 803, Box 40)
  - decorative wood box w/ collage of items from FDR, DDE, NAR, etc, 15 x 11 x 3 (Object 804, Box 40)
  - wooden candy bowl, Gov. Harold LeVander of Minnesota, 9 x 7 (Object 805, Box 34)
  - copper bowl, National Gov's Conference, from Gov of Montana, 1960; 10.25 x 5.5; see #268 (Object 806, Box 34)
  - silver bowl-Alumni Award, Dartmouth College, 1960; 5.5 x 3; see #86 (Object 807, Box 18)
  - dinner plate, 60th National Governors' Conference, Gov Rhodes of Ohio, 1968; 10.5 diameter; see #268 (Object 808, Box 18)
  - dinner plate, Lincoln Sesquicentennial, Gov Stratton of Illinois, 1959; 10.5 diameter (Object 809, Box 18)
  - dinner plate, Cornell University, 1933; 10.5 diameter; see #165, 734 (Object 810, Box 18)
  - dinner plate, Rockland County 350th Hudson-Champlain anniversary., 1959; 10 diameter (Object 811, Box 18)
  - dinner plate, Montana Territorial Centennial, 1964; 10 diameter (Object 812, Box 18)
  - dinner plate, Borough of Queens 50th Anniversary, 1961; 10.25 (Object 813, Box 18)
  - dinner plate with sail boat, 9 diameter (Object 814, Box 18)
  - Gov NAR dinner plate, 10.25 diameter (Object 815, Box 18)
  - dinner plate "Have Peace One With Another", 7.5 diameter (Object 816, Box 18)
  - silver tray, in appreciation from United Jewish Appeal, 7.75; see # 251, 563, 583, 673, 891 (Object 817, Box 18)
  - silver candy dish, in thanks from Cristobal Galarza G., Ecuador, 7 diameter (Object 818, Box 34)
  - silver candy dish, from Kurt Waldheim, United Nations, 1975; 5.5 diameter; in wooden case; see #874 (Object 819, Box 15)
  - miniature beer mug, Syracuse University, 2.25 x 1.75 (Object 820, Box 15)
  - glass candy dish, from "Face the Nation," CBS, 1958 January 12; 3 x 7.5 x 1.25 (Object 821, Box 18)
  - dinner plate, Antonina Uccallo, Hartford CT, 9.5 diameter (Object 822, Box 15)
  - decorative tile, Newport City Council, Rhode Island, 1930?; 6 x 6 (Object 823, Box 15)
  - silver baby bowl "JF Jr" and NAR's initials, 3 diameter (Object 824, Box 15)
  - ceramic ashtray w/ large ceramic potato, inscribed from Maine, 7.5 x 7.5 (Object 825, Box 15)
  - ceramic ashtray, Mount St. Mary College, NY, 6.5 x 6.5 (Object 826, Box 15)
  - ashtray w/pictures of Weighlock Building, Canal Museum, Syracuse, 1962; 4.5 diameter (Object 827, Box 15)
  - ashtray commemorating Battle of 1777, Oriskany NY, 1966 August 6; 6.25 diameter (Object 828, Box 15)
  - ceramic wall hanging of pink roses, from Erie County with note "Trooper Booth, Monsion, for Anderson", 15.25 diameter (Object 829)
  - clear plastic tray, Pres. Mission to Latin America, 1969 Spring; 16.5 x 20.5 x 1.5; see #663, 773 (Object 830)
  - silver bowl, N.A.S.S. 47th Annual Conference, NYS, 12 diameter (Object 831, Box 34)
  - gold tie clip, Erie Canal Sesquicentennial Committee, 1976 July 4 (Object 832, Box 37)
  - metal model of hands in prayer (Object 833, Box 37)
  - miniature model of Dead Sea scrolls in clay pot (Object 834, Box 85)
  - miniature ivory elephant on wood base (Object 835)
  - wooden display stand, from 1/156th ARTY NYARNG, 9.25 x 9.5 x 19; see #790, 791 (Object 836)
  - silver engraved horn, Gov's Fire Prevention Conference, 1959 September 24; 18.5 x 8 diameter (Object 838)
  - carved wood cane w/ cracked handle, 37 long (Object 839)
  - key to Yonkers, NY from Yonkers Republican Committee, 1959 October 31; 60" long (Object 840)
  - large B&W portrait of NAR, 29 diameter (Object 841)
  - 16 cassettes of various NAR recordings & press, w/ transcripts, stored together in hollinger box (Object 842, Box 86)
  - shovel, groundbreaking ceremony, Pocantico Hills School, 1972 January 23 (Object 843)
  - shovel, groundbreaking ceremony, Time & Life Building, Rock Center, 1957 May 16 (Object 844, Box 82)
  - NY state flag from Chautauqua County w/ bronze eagle pole emblem, 36 x 58 (Object 845, Box 81)
  - large NY state flag, 51 x 61 (Object 846, Box 82)
  - large Canadian flag w/ bronze maple leaf emblem, 36 x 72 (Object 847, Box 73)
  - large blue/white flag w/eagle emblem "E Pluribus Unum", 70 x 117.5; stored w/ #854 (Object 848, Box 70)
  - campaign banner "Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating", 133.5 x 89; see #334 (Object 849, Box 71)
  - large white banner w/ snake, eagle, book "Spes Anchora Vitae", 69 x 51 (Object 850, Box 75)
  - large red & white flag "Don't Tread on Me", 30 x 47 (Object 851, Box 71)
  - large blue/white flag w/4 stars, eagle emblem "E Pluribus Unum", 52 x 68.5; stored w/ #850 (Object 852, Box 73)
  - large blue/red/white/yellow flag with gold fringe, 36 x 60 x 24; stored w/ #848 (Object 854)
  - large American flag, 21.5 x 36; stored w/ # 964, 965, 938 (Object 856, Box 79)
  - large American flag w/ 48 stars and gold fringe, 50 x 69 (Object 857, Box 43)
  - 141st Anniversary. Greek Independence sash, 1962; 36 long (Object 860, Box 43)
  - Dartmouth College Banner attached to 19" pole, 28 long; see #86 (Object 861, Box 41)
  - miniature American flag, 4-H flag, 4 x 5.5; see # 519, 627 (Object 862, Box 20)
  - 3 metal eagle statuettes for flag poles, 6 x 5 (Object 863, Box 43)
  - 2 wooden flag stands, 6.75 x 14 diameter (Object 864)
  - commission as Admiral of Flagship Fleet, from American Airlines, 1948 December 21 (Object 865)
  - hand-embroidered pillowcase (Belgian?), 20 x 16 (Object 866, Box 16)
  - red/white/blue knitted pot holder from Bicentennial, 1976; 6.5 x 5.5 (Object 867, Box 35)
  - red/white umbrella w/ 2 notes from "Carolyn Pattie, Nancie Francie", 1973; 36 long (Object 868)
  - notepad, Republican Convention, 1960; 12 x 9 (Object 871, Box 37)
  - metal plaque Las Tres Americas Unidas, Fernando Chi, Costa Rica, 11.25 x 9 (Object 872, Box 34)
  - Project Hope paperweight by Steuben Crystal, 1973 September 25; 9.25 x 6 x 4 (Object 873, Box 16)